STITCH WARRIOR demo is a trial version of a gothic style stitch font. It 's made of cross stitches ("x") and even kerning is based on 1, 2 or 3 stitches I was trying to be as accurate and close to reality as possible.
This demo version is free for personal use only. For commercial and full version please visit:

http://www.rolandhuse.com  
http://www.myfonts.com/foundry/MyHandwritings/

Please contatct me if you have any questions or feedback, also about the following:
- This family does not language ALL extensions, but I am willing to create any extensions on request
- Discovering kerning problems while using 
- Or any other question or feedback. 

You MAY NOT sell this font or claim them as your own.
You MAY NOT edit or rename this font.
You MAY NOT redistribute this font.


Thank you & I hope you like this font,

Roland

http://www.rolandhuse.com
https://www.facebook.com/pages/Runes-And-Fonts/123221817784772
